United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 240 (East Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm 5820 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 240 (East Rochester, NY) Minute Books on Microfilm
1914-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America
UBC Local 240
5820 mf
0.22 cubic feet
4 microfilm reels
Minute books, microfilm.
5713162
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 26, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 06, 2013
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America; UBC Local 240, East Rochester, NY.
5713162
- Vol. 1-5 (1914-1963) (Reel 1)
- Vol. 1, 1914-1920; 1 (Reel 1)
  Scope and Contents
  7/19/1914 - 7/6/1920
- Vol. 2, 1920-1925; 2 (Reel 1)
  7/20/1920 - 9/3/1925
- Vol. 3, 1925-1935; 3 (Reel 1)
  9/17/1925 - 1/7/1935
- Vol. 4, 1935-1946; 4 (Reel 1)
  1/21/1935 - 12/5/1946
- Vol. 5, 1947-1963; 5 (Reel 1)
  1/2/1947 - 3/7/1963
- Vol. 6-7 (1963-1976) (Reel 2)
- Vol. 6, 1963-1970; 1 (Reel 2)
  4/4/1963 - 2/5/1970
- Vol. 7, 1970-1976; 2 (Reel 2)
  3/5/1970 - 1/6/1976
- Negative copy of Reel 1. (Reel 3)
- Negative copy of Reel 2. (Reel 4)